When I come to Clean Health Live last
year, I had 700 followers on Instagram.
Because of you told me to buy a camera,
I went home. Now I'm at 38,000.
Big time. [claps]
I am, at this point, at 700 and 90 subs.
The next time I see you, send me a goal.
To do your title and thumbnails fucking
first.
[laughing]
The title and thumbnail's coming.
Because what you're going to do
is you're going to potentially create a
video, put
a lot of effort into editing it,
the duration of it's going to be fucking
massive.
You're going to take time away from other
important parts of your business to do
it.
Then you're going to get to posting it,
and you're going to go, "Oh." And
then because the very most important thing
is the channel between
someone seeing the content
and wanting to watch it,
you now have to create an
introduction that will pay off the
packaging and the content.
Yes.
So right now, that is a 14-inch cock
and you're a
priest.
[laughing]
Next Clean Health,
I want you to think about a title
that everyone
in this room would go, "Fuck,
I need to watch that." Betting Adam
Sullivan 10
grand that he couldn't do this.
There's one.
Yeah.
All right.
I lied to Brian Mark to get him to fight
James Smith.
[laughing]
There's
so many ways you could do it. And also,
here's one.
So MrBeast reuses the seven same titles,
last one
to leave, 24 hours in,
biggest versus smallest, most expensive
versus cheapest,
and then there's another one about,
what do you call it? What is it
when you give money to charity?
Philanthropic.
So even the top creators just keep rinsing
and repeating the same things over
and over and over again. So really,
you should've found an outlier video
and then
just made it Clean Health somehow.
But don't worry,
I used to do this all the time,
and that's why no one watched my
YouTube.
These guys are good. These guys are good